Would you let it go?
It's not that big a deal.
ROSS: Not that big a deal?
It's amazing.
Okay, you just reach in there,
there's one little maneuver, and bam!
A bra, right out the sleeve.
All right, as far
as I'm concerned,
there is nothing a guy can do
that even comes close. Am I right?
RACHEL: Oh, come on! You guys
can pee standing up.
We can? Okay,
I'm tryin' that.
Okay, you know what
blows my mind?
Women can see breasts
any time they want.
You just look down,
and there they are.
How you get any work
done is beyond me.
Oh, okay, you know what I don't get? The
way guys can do so many mean things,
and then not even care.
Multiple orgasms!
JOEY: There you go.
Sync by chocomoon
www.addic7ed.com
♪ So no one told you
life was going to be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always stuck
in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been your day ♪
♪ Your week, your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too ♪
So, Saturday night,
the big night,
date night, Saturday
night, Sat-ur-day night!
- No plans, huh?
- Not a one.
Not even, say,
breaking up with Janice?
Oh, right, right. Shut up.
Chandler, nobody likes
breaking up with someone.
- You just got to do it.
- No, I know,
but it's just so hard, you know?
I mean, you're sitting there with her,
she has no idea what's happening.
And then you finally get
up the courage to do it,
and there's the horrible awkward moment
when you've handed her the note...
Why do you have to
break up with her?
Be a man, just stop calling.
You know, if you want,
I'll do it with you.
Oh, thanks, but I think she'd feel
like we're gangin' up on her.
No, I mean, you break up with
Janice, and I'll break up with Tony.
Oh, you're breaking
up with Tony?
Yeah, I know. He's sweet, but
it's just not fun anymore, you know?
I don't know if it's me, or his
hunger strike, or...I don't know.
Does anybody want
anything else?
Oh, yeah. Last week you
had a wonderful, nutty,
chocolatey, kind of
cakey pie-thing that...
nothing, just, just...I'm fine.
What's the matter?
Why so scrunchy?
Oh, it's my father. He wants to
give me a Mercedes convertible.
That guy...
he burns me up.
Yeah, well, it's a Mercedes
if I move back home.
Ugh, it was horrible!
He called me "young lady."
Ooh, I hate when my
father calls me that.
Did he give you that whole
"You're-not-up-to-this" thing again?
Oh, yeah, yeah, I got the extended
disco version with three choruses of,
"You'll Never Make
It On Your Own."
[SINGS]
♪ Uh-huh, uh-huh ♪
Hi, Joey.
Oh, my God...Angela.
Wow, being dumped by you
obviously agrees with her.
- Are you going to go over there?
- No.
Yeah. No.
Okay, but not yet. I don't
want to seem too eager.
One-Mississippi, two-Mississippi,
three-Mississippi...
that seems pretty cool.
Hey, Angela.
Joey.
You look good.
That's 'cause I'm wearing
a dress that accents my boobs.
You don't say.
So, uh, Rachel, what are you...
uh, what are you doing tonight?
Oh, big glamour night...
me and Monica at Launderama.
Oh.
You, uh...you want to hear
a freakish coincidence?
Guess who's doing
laundry there, too?
- Who?
- Me!
Was that not clear?
Uh, hey, why don't, uh...
why don't I just
join you...both...there?
Don't you have a laundry
room in your building?
Yes.
I do have a laundry
room in my building,
um, but there's a...
rat problem.
Apparently, they're attracted
to the dryer sheets,
and they're goin' in fine,
but they're comin' out all...
fluffy.
Anyway, say, 7-ish?
Sure.
Forget it, Joey.
I'm with Bob now.
- Bob?
- Mm-hmm.
Who the hell's Bob?
Bob is great.
He's smart, he's sophisticated,
and he has a real job.
You, you go on three auditions a month
and you call yourself an actor. But Bob...
Come on. We were
great together!
And not just at the fun stuff,
but, like, talking, too.
Yeah, well, sorry, Joe. You said,
"Let's just be friends."
So guess what?
- What?
- We're just friends.
Fine. Fine.
So, why don't the four
of us go out and have
dinner together tonight...
you know, as friends?
What "four of us"?
Well, you know, you and Bob,
and me and my girlfriend, uh...
uh...Monica.
JOEY: Monica, I'm tellin' you,
this guy is perfect for you.
Forget it! Not after your cousin
who could belch the alphabet.
Come on. This guy's great.
His name's Bob. He's Angela's...
ahem, brother.
He's smart, he's sophisticated,
and he has a real job.
Me, I go on three auditions a month
and call myself an actor, but Bob is...
- Oh, God help us.
- What?
Ugly Naked Guy is
laying kitchen tile.
BOTH:
Eww!
Look, I'm asking
a favor here.
You know, I'm thinking if I
do this thing for her brother,
maybe Angela will
come back to me.
What's going on here?
You go out with tons of girls.
I know, but...
look, I made a huge mistake. I never
should have broken up with her.
Will you help me?
Please?
Okay. Bye.
Well, Monica's not coming,
it's just going to be me and Rachel.
[ROSS CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Oh. Well, hold on there, camper. Are you
sure you've thought this thing through?
It's laundry. The thinking
through is pretty minimal.
See, it's just you and Rachel,
just the two of you?
This is a date.
You're going on a date.
Nuh-uh.
Yeah-huh.
So, what are you saying here...?
I should shave again,
pick up some wine, what?
Well, you, uh, may want to
rethink the dirty underwear.
This is basically the
first time she's going to
see your underwear.
Do you want it to be dirty?
No.
Oh, and, uh,
the fabric softener?
Okay, okay, now, what
is wrong with my Snuggles?
What, it says I'm a sensitive,
warm kind of guy,
you know, like a
little fuzzy bear.
Okay, I can pick something
else up on the way.
There you go.
MONICA:
Thank you.
So, what does this Bob guy
look like? Is he tall, short?
Yep.
Which?
Which what?
You've never met
Bob, have you?
No, but he's...
Oh, my God, Joey, for all we know,
this guy could be horribly...
Hey, Joey!
Horribly attractive.
I'll be shutting up now.
Where are they?
This is nice. We never do
anything, just the two of us.
It's great. Maybe tomorrow we can
rent a car, and run over some puppies.
Ew. I don't want
to do that.
- Here we go.
- Okay, have a good break-up.
- Hey, Janice.
- Oh, my God, I am so glad you called me.
I had the most
supremely awful day.
Hey, that's not good.
Can I get an espresso and
a latte over here, please?
We got the proofs back
from that photo shoot...
you know, the one with
the little vegetables...
anyway, they pretty
much sucked, so,
I blew off the rest of the
afternoon, and I went shopping.
And I got you...
JANICE:
I'm looking, I'm looking...
I'm looking.
- I got you...
- What?!
- What?
- What...did you get me there?
I got you...
these.
Bullwinkle socks.
- That's so sweet.
- Well, I knew you had the Rockys.
And so I figured, you know, you can
wear Bullwinkle and Bullwinkle,
or you can wear Rocky and Rocky,
or, you can mix and match,
moose and squirrel.
Whatever you want.
That's great.
Well, I'm going to get another
espresso. More latte?
No...
no, I...I'm, I'm still
working on mine.
[JANICE LAUGHS OBNOXIOUSLY]
That's it?
Yeah, it was really hard.
Oh, yeah, the hug
looked pretty brutal.
Okay, you weren't there.
WOMAN:
Comin' through! Move, move!
Oh, excuse me! I was kind
of using that machine.
Yeah, well, now
you're kind of not.
But, I...I saved it.
I put my basket on top.
- Oh, I'm sorry, is that your basket?
- Yes.
It's really pretty.
Unfortunately, I don't see suds!
What?
No suds, no save, okay?
- What's goin' on?
- Hi,
uh, nothing. That horrible
woman just took my machine.
Was your basket on top?
- Yeah, but, there were no suds.
- So?
Well, you know,
"no suds, no save."
No suds, no...excuse me.
Hold on a second!
This is my friend's machine.
Hey, hey, hey!
Her stuff wasn't in it!
Hey, hey, hey! That's not
the rule, and you know it!
All right, show's over.
Nothing to see here.
Okay, let's do laundry.
That was amazing!
I can't even send back soup.
Well, that's because you're
such a sweet, gentle, uh...
um, uh, do you,
uh, do you...
oh, hey, uh, you
must need detergent. Oh!
- What's that?
- Überweiss.
It's new, it's German,
it's extra-tough!
Rach, do you, uh, are
you going to separate those?
Oh, God. Ugh.
Oh, am I being, like a
total laundry spaz?
I mean, am I supposed
to use like one machine
for shirts, and another
machine for pants?
Have you...Rach, have you
never done this before?
Well, not myself, but I
know other people that have.
Okay, you caught me.
I'm a laundry virgin.
Uh, well, don't worry,
I'll use the gentle cycle.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Okay, um...
basically, you want to use
one machine for all your whites.
Whites. Okay.
A whole another machine for,
- for your colors.
- Colors.
And, and then a third for
your, uh, your, uh...
delicates, and that
would be your bras
and your under...panty things.
Okay, well, what about...
these white cotton panties.
Would they go with whites
or with delicates?
Uh, that, that, that...
would be a judgment call.
[ALL LAUGHING]
He's so cute!
So, where did you
guys grow up?
- Brooklyn Heights.
- Cleveland.
Ha. Heh, heh, heh.
- How, how did that happen?
- Oh, my God!
What?
I, uh, suddenly
had the feeling I was...
falling.
But I'm not.
So, you and Angela, huh?
Yep. Pretty much.
- You're a lucky man.
- Yeah.
You know what I miss
the most about her?
That cute nibbly noise
she makes when she eats.
Like a happy little squirrel,
or...or a weasel.
Huh, I never really noticed.
Oh, yeah, yeah, listen for it.
Monica...Monica is great.
Yeah. Yeah, she is.
But it's not going to last.
She's too much
for me in bed.
Sexually.
I've got to tell you.
Bob is terrific.
Yeah, isn't he?
It's so great to meet a guy
who is smart and funny,
and has an emotional
age beyond, like, eight.
You know what else?
He's unbelievable in bed!
Wow!
My brother never even told
me when he lost his virginity.
Huh.
That's nice.
Okay, you can do this. It's just
like pulling off a Band-Aid.
Just do it really fast, and
then the wound is exposed.
Go! Go!
Janice.
Hi, Janice.
Okay, here we go. I don't
think we should go out anymore.
Janice.
All right.
Well...
well, there you go.
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
RACHEL: Okay, I know this is
going to sound really stupid,
but I feel...I feel that if I can
do this...you know,
if I can actually do
my own laundry,
there isn't anything
I can't do.
That does not sound
stupid to me.
You know, it's like...the
first time I had to
make dinner for myself
after Carol left me.
[WASHER BUZZES]
I'm sorry, that's all the time
we have. Next, on "Ross"...
[RACHEL LAUGHS]
Okay.
- Uh-oh.
- What, "uh-oh"?
Uh-oh...
uh-oh...the laundry's done.
It's a...uh, it's a song.
The laundry song
that we sing.
[SINGS]: ♪ Uh-oh, the laundry's done ♪
♪ Uh-oh, uh-oh ♪
Ross, what's the matter?
Nothing, nothing.
[SINGS] ♪ Lee-lo,
the laundry's done ♪
Come on, show me.
All right, all right,
it's just that you left
a red sock in with all
your whites, and now...
- everything's kind of pink.
- Oh.
Everything's pink?
Yeah, uh, except for the
red sock, which is still red.
I'm sorry, please don't be upset.
It could happen to anyone.
Except it didn't.
It happened to me.
Oh, God! I'm going to look like
a big Marshmallow peep.
What am I doing?
My father's right.
I can't live on my own.
I can't even do laundry.
[WOMAN LAUGHS]
[NIBBLING]
Something went wrong
with Underdog,
and they couldn't get
his head to inflate.
So anyway, um...
his head is, like, flopping
down Broadway, right?
And I'm just thinking...
how inappropriate this is.
Um...I've got something
in my eye, uh, Joey,
could we check it in
the light, please?
- Oh, my God!
- What?
Hello! Were we at
the same table? It's like...
cocktails in Appalachia.
- Come on, they're close.
- Close? She's got her tongue in his ear.
Oh. Like you've never gotten
a little rambunctious with Ross?
Joey, this is sick.
It's disgusting. It's, it's...
not really true, is it?
Well, who's to say
what's true? I mean...
Oh, my God, what
were you thinking?
All right, look. I'm not
proud of this, okay?
Well, maybe I am a little.
- Oh!
- Ow!
- I'm out of here.
- Wait, wait, wait! Come on!
You want him. I want her.
He likes you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'm thinking, if we put our heads
together, between the two of us,
we can break them up.
MONICA: I'm so sorry.
I can't believe I did this.
But I just couldn't stop laughing
at your Norman Mailer story.
[NIBBLING]
Uh, waiter, one more plate
of chicken wings over here.
Here's the thing, Janice. You know,
I mean, it's like we're different.
I'm like the bing, bing, bing.
You're like the boom, boom...boom.
- JANICE: Ow!
- Oh!
- Oh, my God!
- Ow!
- I'm so sorry!
- Are you okay?
- Ow!
Um, it's just my lens.
It's just my lens.
I'll be right back.
Ow.
I hit her in the eye.
I hit her in the eye!
This is the worst break-up
in the history of the world!
Oh, my God.
How many of those
have you had?
Oh, I don't know.
A million?
Chandler, shh, shh. Easy, easy.
Go to your happy place.
[HUMMING]
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
- All right.
I'm not fine. Here she comes.
Just wait here, okay? Breathe.
[PHOEBE & JANICE SPEAKING
INAUDIBLY]
How do you do that?
It's like a gift.
We should always, always
break up together.
Oh, I'd like that!
ROSS: You got the clothes clean.
Now, that's the important part.
Oh, I guess. Except everything
looks like jammies now.
Whoa, I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
We had this cart.
Yeah, well, I had a 24-inch
waist. You lose things.
Now, come on.
Get out of my way.
I'm sorry, you know, maybe I wasn't
being clear. Uh, this is our cart.
Hey, hey, hey, there
weren't any clothes in it!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Quit making up rules!
Let go! Come on, it's my cart.
You know I saw it first.
All right, listen, Missy,
if you want this cart,
you're going to have
to take me with it!
Yes! Did you see that?
You were incredible!
A brand new woman,
ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you. I could not
have done this without you.
ROSS:
Okay, um...
uh...more clothes
in the dryer?
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
No.
- Oh, are you sure you're okay?
- Yeah.
- Does it still hurt?
What a neat idea. All your
clothes match. I'm going to do this.
MONICA:
Hi!
PHOEBE:
Hey, how did it go?
Excellent.
We ripped that couple apart,
and kept the pieces for ourselves.
What a beautiful story.
Hey, I'm fine, by the way.
Oh, I'm...sorry.
- Where's Chandler?
- Oh, he needed some time to grieve.
CHANDLER:
I'm free! I'm free!
That ought to do it.
Sync by chocomoon
www.addic7ed.com